hahaonline.co.uk 2009-11-29

# ha ha bar & grill, privacy policy

You are here: Home > Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

We are sensitive to privacy issues on the internet and are committed to protecting your privacy.

### Data Collected

We collect your personal data, which you voluntarily provide to us for registration or other participation in any online interactive activity. We may use this data to email you newsletters and other information you may have requested and to respond to your specific requests. In addition we may contact you in the form of telephone calls if this is your preferred method of contact.

### Data Disclosure

We own and manage the data collected on our site and do not disclose this data to third parties unless required by law or court order or to allow third parties to provide services to us. Information gained by online surveys or competitions enable us to gain a better understanding of our visitors.

### IP Addresses

IP addresses allow us to analyse trends, manage our site and better understand the needs and profiles of our customers.

### Links to other web sites

Our site may contain links to other sites. We are not responsible for their privacy practices.

### Changes to our privacy statement

We may revise our Privacy Police at any time. On entering this site, you are responsible for checking this policy.

### Cookies

Our site uses cookies. A 'cookie' is a small file that a web site can send to your browser helping us to recognise you as a prior visitor and improve our site for your benefit. You may be able to set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie.

### Access Rights

You have a right to access the personal data that is held about you. Please write to us at the following address to obtain a copy of the personal information ha ha holds about you: Bay Restaurant Group, Porter Tun House, 500 Capability Green, Luton, LU1 3LS enclosing your postal details.
